lovelywholesale.com 2015-06-02

# Privacy Policy _Our Store_FAQ_Help Center_LovelyWholesale | Wholesale Shoes,Wholesale Clothing, Cheap Clothes,Cheap Shoes Online. - LovelyWholesale.com

Privacy Policy   
Lily / 2011-07-14

Privacy  
Lovelywholesale.com is committed to protecting our site visitors & customers privacy. Information about customers will not be disclosed to any third parties accept to fulfill the delivery of goods to you, customer research, carrying out credit & security checks and where necessary to process debit or credit card payments. By placing an order with us you consent to us collecting and using personal data about you as specified below in accordance with this policy statement. Any changes made to these terms will be posted here so that you are always kept informed about the collection and use of your personal information.

**Secure Socket Layer (SSL)** , to process securely online credit card transaction. Your payment details is encrypted and cannot be read as it travels over the internet. Credit card numbers are not held in clear text within our web site. 

How is information we collect about you used?  
When an order is placed with us we need to collect your name, address, telephone number and email address, and details of your chosen method of payment. This information is needed for us to process and fulfill your chosen order. We will use your email address to send your order status notification to you. If any problems arise with the fulfillment of your order we will contact you via email of phone. The information provided by you may be passed to third party service providers for the purpose of processing your chosen order of goods. If you have made a purchase from our website we may occasionally email you with updates of our latest product range, news and special offers.If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, you can click the unsubscribe link.

Third Parties  
The details you provide to us will not be sold to third party organisations; they may only be shared for the purpose of processing your chosen order as outlined above. Our site may contain links to and from other websites, advertisers and third parties, in following these links you must also view that websites own privacy policies as we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.

Inaccuracies and corrections  
We aim to keep your personal data accurate and up to date. If you become aware of errors or inaccuracies, please contact us by clicking on the "[ _Contact Us_](http://www.lovelywholesale.com/article-7-Contact+Us.html)" link in the menu. Or through the following methods:

Tel: 1-516-299-9077 or 1-619-828-3688

Email: support@lovelywholesale.com

ADD: Rm.19C Lockhart Ctr.,301-307 Lockhart Rd.,Wan Chai Hong Kong

How do I unsubscribe?  
You can unsubscribe by using the link from any email newsletter or your personal subscribe setting after logged in.
